<form>
	<header>
			<title>Consent for Participation in the NextGen Cohort Study</title>
	</header>
	<pages>
		<page>
			<img src="images/consent_begin.png width"273 width height=157> </img>
			<title>Welcome to The Yet to be Named Study</title>
			<content> Researchers at ___ and the National Cancer Institute (NCI) are doing this research study to understand the causes of cancer and other diseases. We are working with your health care provider to enroll about 150,000 people. We hope it will help improve the health of current and future generations.

			The following pages will give you information about the study so that you can decide whether you would like to take part. In each section, you can click “Learn more” if you wish to get more detailed information. You can also find more information on the study website at XXX.gov

			If you prefer to download and print the entire consent form, please click here
			</content>
		</page>
		
		<page>
			<img src="images/eMed_records.png" width="153" height="153" alt="Medical Records">
			<img src="images/blood_donation.png" width="153" height="153" alt="Blood Draw">
			<content>
				To help us better understand certain health conditions, we need to learn more about you. In the study, we will ask you to:

				1.	Fill out surveys. These will ask about things like your regular habits, your medical history, and where you have lived. 
				2.	Provide biological samples (such as blood, urine, stool and saliva). 
				3.	Allow us to access your medical records, which will provide key details of your health. 
				
				If you decide to participate, and complete this consent, you will receive further instructions on how to complete the first survey and provide your first biological specimens. 

				Once you start the study, we hope you will remain a part of it for many years, even if you change your health care provider. We will periodically contact you to inform you about the study’s progress and ask you to complete more surveys, provide additional samples, and/or request your participation in additional study visits.
			</content>
		</page>

	</pages>
	<footer>FOOTER GOES HERE </footer>
</form>